SFU Archives reference and display materials collection
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Portraits, [ca 1960] - 2002; F-247-1; 1.55 m of textual records 1254 photographs 412 contact sheets 137 negatives 56 slides
  - Education, 1965 - 1991; F-247-1-22; 13 cm of textual records 86 photographs 61 contact sheets 6 negatives
    - Kirchner, Glenn; Physical Development Centre, also Professor Emeriti, 1965 - [ca 1989]; F-247-1-22-0-23 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: Helcermanas, IMC 83064-3, LIDC.
    - Kootnekoff, J.L., [ca 1965] - [ca 1966]; F-247-1-22-0-24 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
    - MacKinnon, Archibald; Educational Foundations Centre; Dean, 1966 - 1970; F-247-1-22-0-25 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: Helcermanas, LIDC 68065.
    - Martin, Jack, [ca 1979]; F-247-1-22-0-26 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 79055-2.
    - McClaren, Milton, [ca 1969] - [ca 1979]; F-247-1-22-0-27 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: 69026, IMC 79054-21.
    - O'Connell, M. Sheila, [ca 1979]; F-247-1-22-0-28 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 79054-22.
    - Prock, Leone, 1968 - [ca 1979]; F-247-1-22-0-29 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 79056-12.
    - Robinson, Norm, [ca 1979]; F-247-1-22-0-30 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 79054-11.
    - Sandvoss, Joachim (Joe), [ca 1978] - [ca 1979]; F-247-1-22-0-31 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: UNS; IMC 79055-31.
    - Savage, Paul; Physical Development Centre, Athletics Head Swim Coach, [ca 1965] - [ca 1982]; F-247-1-22-0-32 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: Helcermanas; SF Week, Comment.
    - Shapson, Stan, 1979 - 1989; F-247-1-22-0-33 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC, M&PR.
    - Stratton, Steve, [ca 1966] - [ca 1969]; F-247-1-22-0-34 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
    - Trivett, John F.; Professor Emeriti, [ca 1979] - [ca 1989]; F-247-1-22-0-35 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: IMC 79054-18; UNS 80214-3; M&PR, Comment.
    - Tuinman, Jaap; Dean, [ca 1979] - [ca 1991]; F-247-1-22-0-36 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: IMC 79055-3; UNS 85112-7.
    - Walker, Tom C.; Physical Development Centre, [ca 1965] - [ca 1966]; F-247-1-22-0-37 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
    - Wasserman, Selma, [ca 1979]; F-247-1-22-0-38 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
    - Whitney, Al, [ca 1979]; F-247-1-22-0-39 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 79053-17.
    - Wideen, Marvin, 1979; F-247-1-22-0-40 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 79053-8.
    - Wyatt, Jane, 1979; F-247-1-22-0-41 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: LIDC 79054-23.
    - Professors Emeriti, Education; negatives, [ca 1979]; F-247-1-22-0-42 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
  - Gerontology Research Centre, 1985 - 1990; F-247-1-23; 1 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of articles and published material relating to individuals from the Gerontology Research Centre. For a list of faculty members associated with the sub-series, see access points.
    Hodge, Gerald; Holliday, Stephen
    - Hodge, Gerald, 1988 - 1990; F-247-1-23-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: M&PR.
    - Holliday, Stephen, 1985; F-247-1-23-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-5)
      Creator's original file classification code: SF Week, July 25, 1985.
  - Library Faculty, 1964 - 1989; F-247-1-24; 3 cm of textual records 37 photographs 64 contact sheets 8 negatives
    Sub-series consists of photos, negatives, documents, and published material relating to individuals from the University Library. For a list of faculty members associated with the sub-series, see access points.
    Don Baird; Dobb, Theodore C.; Finlayson, Marilynne; Gray, Helen; Kassis, S.; Laskowski, Seno; MacDonald, C.W.; Mather, Dan; Philips, Brian F.; Pyrch, Jeannette; Wawryzysko, Aleksandra; Whiteley, W.H.; University Library
    - Baird, Donald; University Librarian/Archivist, 1964 - 1981; F-247-1-24-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: Williams Bros., Helcermanas, AVC.
    - Dobb, Ted; University Librarian, [ca 1966] - [ca 1978]; F-247-1-24-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: Helcermanas, PPS.
    - Finlayson, Marilynne (nee Peterson), [ca 1966]; F-247-1-24-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Gray, Helen, [ca 1966]; F-247-1-24-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Kassis, S., [ca 1966]; F-247-1-24-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Laskowski, Seno, [ca 1966]; F-247-1-24-0-6 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - MacDonald, C.W., 1966 - 1989; F-247-1-24-0-7 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: Helcermanas; SF Week.
    - Mather, Dan, 1966; F-247-1-24-0-8 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Philips, Brian F., 1966; F-247-1-24-0-9 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Pyrch, Jeannette, 1966; F-247-1-24-0-10 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Wawryzysko, Aleksandra, 1966; F-247-1-24-0-11 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Whiteley, W.H., 1966; F-247-1-24-0-12 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Library Faculty / Staff, 1965 - 1966; F-247-1-24-0-13 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: Helcermanas, IMC.
  - Archives, 1998; F-247-1-25; 3 photographs
    Sub-series consists of photos relating to individuals from the Archives staff. For a list of administrative officers associated with the sub-series, see access points.
    Fournier, Frances; Archives and Records Management Department
    - Fournier, Frances & Matt "x" [fundraising for Peak], 1998; F-247-1-25-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
  - Administrative Officers, 1964 - 1992; F-247-1-26; 12 cm of textual records 124 photographs 9 contact sheets 17 negatives
    Sub-series consists of photos, contact sheets, negatives, proofs, articles, and published material relating to administrative officers of the University. For a list of administrative officers associated with the sub-series, see access points.
    Barton, Norman; Bell, Susan; Blaney, Jack P.; Boyle, Peter S.; Branscombe, Joyce E.; Cairns, Marilyn; Calvert, Thomas W.; Campbell, Emily A.; Chase, John; Davies, Lorne W.; Devenyi, Denes; Devries, William; Doerr, Audrey D.; Ellis, G.O.; Evans, Harry M.; Griba, Walter; Harmon, Thomas P.; Heath, W. Ronald; Heffelfinger, Jane S.; Hendy, C.M.; Heselgrave, Barry A.C.; Hoegg, Jo Lynne; Hyde, Naida; Jewell, T. Ross; Johnson, J.E.; Jones, Wilard E.; Klassen, William; Kloeble, Walter M.; Laws, Donna; Lawton, Merlin; Leach, Joy B.; Liotta, Christine M.; Lipinski, Edward; Lipinski, Bea G.; Loewen, Vern; Marusyk, Harry A.; McKeown, Brian A.; McRae, Edward D.; Mennell, Ken; Mitchell, David; Munro, John M.; Orr, A.G.; Palmer, W.I.; Paulson, Gordon R.; Rees, Joe; Roberts, Dennis; Roberts, Stanley; Robertson, D. P.; Ross, Donald H.; Scott, Ernest M.; Stewart, William A.; Suart, George; Tolan, Lionel; Turner, E.; Ward, Roger W.; Wattamaniuk, Walter J.; Wheatley, Jon; Willett, Sandy; Williams, Ian; Wilson, Brian G.; Young, Bruce; Yule, William A.
    - Barton, Norman; Registrar, 1965; F-247-1-26-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: William Bros..
    - Bell, Susan; Alumni Relations, [197-]; F-247-1-26-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Blaney, J.P.; Dean of Continuing Studies, VP Development, 1975 - [ca 1980]; F-247-1-26-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: UNS 75009.
    - Boyle, Peter, [198-]; F-247-1-26-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Branscombe, Joyce E.; Daycare, 1986; F-247-1-26-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: IMC 86132-9.
    - Cairns, A. Marilyn; Academic Advice, [ca 1976]; F-247-1-26-0-6 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Calvert, Thomas W.; Dean of IDS, VP Research, [ca 1975] - [ca 1981]; F-247-1-26-0-7 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: UNS 81219-4a.
    - Campbell, Emily; Daycare, [198-]; F-247-1-26-0-8 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Chase, John; Analytical Studies, [198-]; F-247-1-26-0-9 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Davies, Lorne; Athletics, Football Coach, 1965 - 1968; F-247-1-26-0-10 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Devenyi, Denes; Former Assistant Director, Physical Plant & Planning, [ca 1977] - 1986; F-247-1-26-0-11 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Devries, William; Admin. Services, [ca 1970] - [ca 1985]; F-247-1-26-0-12 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: IMC 70011-6, UNS 85247-9.
    - Doerr, Audrey; Political Science, Associate Dean of Grad Studies, 1979 - 1986; F-247-1-26-0-13 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Ellis, G.O.; Personnel, [ca 1969]; F-247-1-26-0-14 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Evans, Harry M.; Registrar, 1969 - 1990; F-247-1-26-0-15 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: IMC 69069-8.
    - Griba, Walter; Instructional Media Centre, [ca 1975]; F-247-1-26-0-16 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: IMC.
    - Harmon, Thomas P.; Health Services, [ca 1975]; F-247-1-26-0-17 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Heath, W. Ronald; Registrar, 1985; F-247-1-26-0-18 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: IMC 85062-3.
    - Heffelfinger, Jane S.; Development, [198-]; F-247-1-26-0-19 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Hendy, C. Martin; Cooperative Education, [198-]; F-247-1-26-0-20 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Heselgrave, Barry A.C.; Computing Services, [198-]; F-247-1-26-0-21 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Hoegg, Jo Lynne; Dean of Continuing Studies, 1985; F-247-1-26-0-22 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: UNS 85027-3.
    - Hyde, Naida; Counseling, 1986; F-247-1-26-0-23 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: IMC 86143.
    - Jewell, T. Ross; Computing Services, [ca 1979]; F-247-1-26-0-24 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Johnson, J.E.; Facilities Management, [ca 1985]; F-247-1-26-0-25 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Jones, Wilard E.; Computing Services, 1978 - 1992; F-247-1-26-0-26 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: M&PR, SF Week.
    - Klassen, William; Development, [ca 1985]; F-247-1-26-0-27 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Kloeble, Walter M.; Comptroller, 1986; F-247-1-26-0-28 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: IMC 86135-8.
    - Laws, Donna M.; Ceremonies, [ca 1970] - [ca 1980]; F-247-1-26-0-29 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Lawton, Merlin; Health Services, [ca 1969]; F-247-1-26-0-30 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Leach, Joy B.; Development, [ca 1988]; F-247-1-26-0-31 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Liotta, Christine M.; Alumni Relations, 1984; F-247-1-26-0-32 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: IMC 84088-8.
    - Lipinski, Bea G.; Counseling, [198-]; F-247-1-26-0-33 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Lipinski, Edward; Health Services, [198-]; F-247-1-26-0-34 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Loewen, Vern C.; Financial Aid, [ca 1986]; F-247-1-26-0-35 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Marusyk, Harry A.; Computing Services, [ca 1966]; F-247-1-26-0-36 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - McKeown, Brian A.; Animal Care Faculty, [ca 1986]; F-247-1-26-0-37 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: IMC 86133.
    - McRae, Edward D.; Development, [197-?]; F-247-1-26-0-38 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Mennell, Kenneth J.; Media and Public Relations, [ca 1988]; F-247-1-26-0-39 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Mitchell, David, [199-]; F-247-1-26-0-40 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Munro, John M.; VP Academic, Dean of Arts, [ca 1986]; F-247-1-26-0-41 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Orr, Arthur G.; Physical Plant and Planning, 1964 - 1965; F-247-1-26-0-42 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: H.L. McDonald; Williams Bros..
    - Palmer, W.I.; Development, [ca 1979]; F-247-1-26-0-43 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Paulson, Gordon R.; Comptroller, [ca 1979]; F-247-1-26-0-44 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Rees, Joe, [ca 1966]; F-247-1-26-0-45 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Roberts, Dennis; Media and Public Relations, [ca 1979]; F-247-1-26-0-46 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: UNS.
    - Roberts, Stanley; VP University Services, [ca 1975]; F-247-1-26-0-47 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: Bill Cunningham.
    - Robertson, D.P. (Pat); Registrar, [ca 1965]; F-247-1-26-0-48 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: Peter Knowlden of Peak.
    - Ross, Donald H.; Bursar, 1968; F-247-1-26-0-49 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: Schiffer(?) Photographer Ltd..
    - Scott, Ernie; Director of Finance, 1983 - 1986; F-247-1-26-0-50 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: UNS 83.3.14-20.
    - Stewart, William A.; Student Services, [ca 1974]; F-247-1-26-0-51 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Suart George; VP Administration, [ca 1976] - [ca 1987]; F-247-1-26-0-52 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Tolan, Lionel, [197-?]; F-247-1-26-0-53 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Turner, E.; Media & Public Relations, [ca 1980]; F-247-1-26-0-54 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Ward, Roger W.; Budget Director, [ca 1984]; F-247-1-26-0-55 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Wattamaniuk, Walter J.; Analytical Studies, 1986; F-247-1-26-0-56 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: IMC 86134-12.
    - Wheatley, John; Dean of Graduate Studies, 1976 - 1980; F-247-1-26-0-57 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Willett, S.; Development (Resources), 1972; F-247-1-26-0-58 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Williams, Ian R.; Computing Services, 1985; F-247-1-26-0-59 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: UNS 86224-10a.
    - Wilson, Brian G.; VP Academic, [197-] - [ca 1978]; F-247-1-26-0-60 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
      Creator's original file classification code: Campbell, UNS.
    - Young, Bruce; Personnel, [ca 1975]; F-247-1-26-0-61 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
    - Yule, William A.; Personnel, [198-?]; F-247-1-26-0-62 (Archival box - standard 247-6)
  - Board of Governors, 1963 - 1984; F-247-1-27; 6 cm of textual records 34 photographs 2 negatives
    Sub-series consists of photos, contact sheets, articles, documents, and published material relating to the Board of Governors. For a list of individuals associated with the sub-series, see access points.
    Block-Bauer, C.; Branca, Angelo E.; Colins, Mark; Daem, Jean-Pierre; Dietrich, F.H.; Dougherty, Peter; Eyre, A.M.; Frederickson, Clarence J.; Hean, A.F.C.; Lester, Richard E.; McLean, Cyrus; Rolston, R.C.; Sutherland, G.A.; Wong, George D.; Wood, Beth; Board of Governors
    - Board of Governors (group and individual images), [ca 1963] - [ca 1984]; F-247-1-27-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
      Creator's original file classification code: Herbert L. McDonald; Pacific Photographic Services Ltd.; Val Tkatschow Photography Ltd..
    - Block-Bauer, C., 1965 - 1968; F-247-1-27-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
    - Branca, Hon. Justice Angelo E., 1967; F-247-1-27-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
      Creator's original file classification code: AVC 67512-6.
    - Colins, Mark, [ca 1968] - [ca 1970]; F-247-1-27-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
      Creator's original file classification code: Tony Culher?.
    - Daem, Jean-Pierre, 1975; F-247-1-27-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
      Creator's original file classification code: H. Roy Stephens.
    - Dietrich, F.H., 1965; F-247-1-27-0-6 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
      Creator's original file classification code: Vancouver Sun.
    - Dougherty, Peter, 1975; F-247-1-27-0-7 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
    - Eyre, A.M., [ca 1965] - [ca 1970]; F-247-1-27-0-8 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
      Creator's original file classification code: Whitefoot Studio.
    - Frederickson, Clarence J., 1968; F-247-1-27-0-9 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
      Creator's original file classification code: Mauritz Burlin.
    - Hean, A.F.C., [ca 1965] - [ca 1970]; F-247-1-27-0-10 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
      Creator's original file classification code: Nicholas Rosmo.
    - Lester, Richard E.; Chair, 1963; F-247-1-27-0-11 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
      Creator's original file classification code: Fred S. Schiffer, F.R.P.S..
    - McLean, Cyrus, 1972; F-247-1-27-0-12 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
    - Rolston, R.C., [ca 1970]; F-247-1-27-0-13 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
      Creator's original file classification code: Ronald R Miller.
    - Sutherland, G.A., 1963; F-247-1-27-0-14 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
      Creator's original file classification code: Gade of Skipsey Studio.
    - Wong, George D., [ca 1963] - [ca 1970]; F-247-1-27-0-15 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
    - Wood, Beth, [ca 1963] - [ca 1965]; F-247-1-27-0-16 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
  - Chancellors and Presidents, 1964 - 1993; F-247-1-28; 6 cm of textual records 160 photographs 6 contact sheets 17 negatives 56 slides
    Sub-series consists of photos, contact sheets, articles, documents, and published material relating to past chancellors and presidents of SFU. For a list of individuals associated with the sub-series, see access points.
    Caple, Kenneth P.; Coté, Paul T.; Diamond, Jack; Hamilton, William M.; Jewett, Pauline; Pedersen, Knud George; Rae, Barbara J.; Saywell, William George; Segal, Joseph; Shrum, Gordon; Strand, Kenneth; Stubbs, John O.; McTaggart-Cowan, Patrick
    - Caple, Kenneth, [ca 1970] - [ca 1980]; F-247-1-28-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
      Creator's original file classification code: Franz Linder, Peak?, Fred S. Schiffer, F.R.P.S..
    - Cote, Paul, [ca 1978] - [ca 1984]; F-247-1-28-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
    - Diamond, Jack, 1974 - 1978; F-247-1-28-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
    - Hamilton, Hon. William, 1966 - 1987; F-247-1-28-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
    - Jewett, Pauline; President, 1974 - 1978; F-247-1-28-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
      Creator's original file classification code: Fred S. Schiffer, F.R.P.S.; Vancouver Sun, UNS, Olaffs.
    - McTaggart-Cowan, Patrick D., 1964 - 1968; F-247-1-28-0-6 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
      Creator's original file classification code: Fred S. Schiffer, F.R.P.S.; H.L. McDonald, Jack Lindsay, Helcermanas.
    - Pedersen, K. George (images), 1979 - 1982; F-247-1-28-0-7 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
    - Pedersen, K. George (textual), 1978 - 1984; F-247-1-28-0-8 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
    - Golden Handshake Party - Pedersen, 1983; F-247-1-28-0-9 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
    - Rae, Barbara, [ca 1987]; F-247-1-28-0-10 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
    - Saywell, William G., 1983 - [199-?]; F-247-1-28-0-11 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
    - Segal, Joseph, [199-?]; F-247-1-28-0-12 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
    - Shrum, Gordon; slides, negatives, 1965 - 1986; F-247-1-28-0-13 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
      Creator's original file classification code: Fred S. Schiffer, Graphic.
    - Strand, K.T., 1969 - 1983; F-247-1-28-0-14 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
      Creator's original file classification code: IMC 83039-10; Fred S. Schiffer; Franz Linder; Helcermanas.
    - Stubbs, John, 1993; F-247-1-28-0-15 (Archival box - standard 247-7)
  - Honorary Degree Recipients, 1964 - 2002; F-247-1-29; 64 cm of textual records 309 photographs 2 contact sheets 66 negatives
    Sub-series consists of photos, documents, and notes about Honorary Degree Recipients from SFU from 1965-2002. For a list of Honorary Degree Recipients associated with the sub-series, see access points.
    Bennett, W.A.C.; Macdonald, John B.; Pearkes, George R.; Peterson, Leslie R.; Lovat, Lord; Madge Hogarth; Koerner, Leon; McLuhan, Herbert Marshall; Frederickson, Clarence J.; MacMillan, Harvey Reginald; Waterman, Max; Khorana, Har Gobind; McKenzie, Robert; Ronning, Chester A.; Stevens, Henry H.; Watt, Kenneth E.F.; George, Dan; Ireland, Willard; Murray, Margaret; Ormsby, Margaret; Shrum, Gordon; Herzberg, Gerhard; MacInnis, Grace; Colville, Alex; Erickson, Arthur; Smith, Gordon A.; Diamond, Jack; Wilson, John O.; Winch, Harold; Branca, Angelo E.; Laskin, Bora; Nemetz, Nathaniel; Proudfoot, Patricia M.; Lachs, Manfred; Caple, Kenneth P.; Lane, Elizabeth; Lawrence, Margaret; Williams, Guy R.; Christensen, Jorgen Vibe; Halpern, Ida; Hean-Chatterton, Arnold; Sandwell, Percy; Shadbolt, Jack; Wilson, John Tuzo; Adaskin, Harry; Berger, Tom; McLean, Cyrus; Prittie, Robert; Thompson, Syd; Hoar, William; Koerner, Iby; Lett, Evelyn; MacNeish, Richard; Meredith, John; Scott, Francis; Armstrong, Elsje; Bunge, Mario Augusto; Currie, Lauchlin; McTaggart-Cowan, Ian; Miranda, Louis; Atherley, Gordon R.C.; Gilles, James; Hamilton, William M.; Lambert, Allen T.; McArthur, John; Rogers, Robert; Stevenson, Anne M.; Wilson, Edward O.; Belkin, Morris; Emmott, Alan Herbert; Goodlad, John Inkster; Strand, Kenneth; Webster, John Edgar; Beinder, Frank; Evans, Hubert R.; Gunning, Harry Emmet; Schreyer, Ed; Evans, Harry M.; Friesen, John K.; Hartley, Fred Lloyd; Pentland, Barbara; Reuber, Grant Louis; Roche, Douglas James; Barrett, Dave; Bene, John Gustav; Duckworth, Muriel; Eyre, A.M.; Koshland, Daniel Edward Jr.; Bligh, John; Franklin, Ursula; Gutteridge, May Cecilia; Livesay, Dorothy; Rust, Thomas Grant; McClelland, Jack Gordon; Moonen, Fred H.; Segal, Joseph; Slabbert, Frederik Van Zyl; Belzberg, Samuel; Forrester, Maureen; Fouks, Arthur; Frum, Barbara; Maillet, Antonine; Parkinson, Ray; Dye, Kenneth Malcolm; Kenney-Wallace, Geraldine Anne; Page, Patricia Kathleen; Petch, Howard Earle; Baker, Ron; Gzowski, Peter; Boyd, Liona; Cotler, Irwin; Filer, Mary; Sales, Harold Spence; Jewett, Pauline; Lam, David; Rowland, F. Sherwood; Douglas, James Jardine; Eppich, Helmut; Eppich, Hugo; Reid, Bill; Culver, Dennis F.; Ellis, A. John; Halperin, Maurice; Simons, Thomas Allen; Tennant, Veronica; August, Aimee; Smith, John Maynard; Bartlett, Neil; Bursill-Hall, Geoffrey L.; Connell, Martin P.; Hudson, Donald J.; Kimura, Doreen; Kogawa, Joy; Lewis, Stephen; Coghill, Joy; Davidson, Robert; Phelps, Michael; Shadbolt, Doris; Gelbart, Dan; Smith, Michael; Thomas, Audrey; Campagnolo, Iona; Fellegi, Ivan; McDonald, Wendy; Norris, Len; Nuytten, Phil; Vogt, Erich; Yu, Wei; Laidler, Keith; McCarthy, Grace; McDonald, Hugh; Saywell, William George; R. Murray Schafer; Anderson, Doris; Ballard, Geoffrey; Mintzberg, Henry; Carkner, Robert; Hagan, Stan; Overhauser, Albert; Rae, Barbara J.; Rieckhoff, Klaus E.; Wong, Milton K.; Diamond, Gordon; Duthie, Celia; Eng, Peter; Fraser, John; Levy, Julia; Mattrick, Don; MacDonald, John S.; Strate, Grant; Broadbent, Ed; Gosnell, Joseph; Marcuse, Judith; McLachlin, Beverley; Payette, Julie; Spencer, Kenneth; Suzuki, David; Kerr, Jake; Saul, John Ralston; Maiman, Theodore; Oberlander, Cornelia; Segal, Rosalie; Ling, Victor; Reid, Angus; Taylor, Carole; Tilghman, Shirley; Tong, Kooi Ong; McTaggart-Cowan, Patrick